Joshua Danao

joshdanao29@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/josh-danao portfolio/joshdanao.com github.com/AJRJ29

A software engineer and former courier with a passion for collaboration with both clients and developers in order to create interesting solutions through projects made with JavaScript, React, SQL, and other technologies. My time as a software engineer has allowed me to strengthen both my technical expertise, along with my soft-skills including effective multidisciplinary collaboration, maintaining proper expectations, and ensuring client satisfaction.

Skills:

JavaScript, HTM, CSS, Express, Sequelize, MongoDB, Python, React, Next.js, Bootstrap, Materialize, Node, CanvasEJS, Git/GitHub, Postgre, SQL, React Native

Projects:

Stay Inside:

Full-Stack app allowing users to create and join other created indoor events. Utilize PostgreSQL, Sequelize and Jikan API.

MyAnime:

Full-Stack app allows users to add their favorite anime and manga to their profile. Written in JavaScript with a Node Express back-end and Mongo database.

Work Experience:

May 2020 - August2020

General Assembly - Software Engineer 1218 3rd Ave, Seattle, WA 98101

Three-month, 500-hour full-time and full-stack program conducted in a remote setting, providing experience with the latest front- and back-end programming languages, tools, and methodologies including: JavaScript, HTM, CSS, Express, Sequelize, MongoDB, Python, React, Next.js, Bootstrap, Materialize, Node, CanvasEJS, Git/GitHub, Postgre, SQL, React Native.

Sept 2017 - Nov 2019

FedEx - courier

6841 N Tongass Hwy, Ketchikan, AK

Responsible for picking up and delivering packages at homes and businesses on the delivery route. I was awarded with safe driving for 2 consecutive years and also got the Bravo Zulu award for outstanding performance beyond normal job expectations.

Education:

General Assembly Software Engineer Immersive May 2020 - August 2020